=The Origin of Eternity=
= أصل الخلود =
=Episode 6=
= الحلقة 6 =
Tell me.
أخبرني.
How do you explain that?
كيف تفسر ذلك؟
♪Migrating swan geese fly before my eager eyes♪
♪ إوز البجعة المهاجرة تطير أمام عيني المتلهفة ♪
♪But never return after spring♪
♪ لكن لا تعود بعد الربيع
♪Under the lonely waxing crescent, with a worried and pale face♪
تحت الهلال المنعزل ، ووجهه شاحب وقلق
♪I have no one to drink with♪
♪ ليس لدي من أشرب معه ♪
♪My yearnings are scattered when the sun goes down♪
تشتت أشواقي عند غروب الشمس
Will you forgive me now?
هل ستسامحني الآن؟
I never know the righteous hero
انا لا اعرف البطل الصالح ابدا
is actually a cad.
هو في الواقع نذل.
Yes.
نعم.
I'm a cad.
أنا نذل.
Who only belongs to you.
من ينتمي لك فقط.
♪And more, I fear travelling the world alone♪
♪ وأكثر من ذلك ، أخشى السفر حول العالم وحدي
♪Reminiscing the memories amidst tipsiness♪
♪ استحضار الذكريات وسط النشوة ♪
♪Missing out on the loved one while growing old♪
♪ فقدان من تحب أثناء تقدمك في العمر ♪
♪I fear the past perishes in a flash♪
♪ أخشى أن يموت الماضي في ومضة ♪
Qinghuan.
تشينغوان.
Remember this.
تذكر هذا.
I, Bai Ze will
أنا باي زي سوف
do such deviant acts
تفعل مثل هذه الأعمال المنحرفة
only to you.
لك وحدك.
Bai Ze.
باي زي.
You're in there, right? Answer me, Bai Ze.
أنت هناك ، أليس كذلك؟  أجبني ، باي زي.
- Martial Sister. - Is that woman inside here too?
- شقيقة عسكرية.  - هل تلك المرأة بالداخل هنا أيضًا؟
- Does she want you to be quiet? - Martial Sister.
- هل تريدك أن تصمت؟  - شقيقة عسكرية.
- Stop it. - Bai Ze, open the door.
- توقف عن ذلك.  - باي زي ، افتح الباب.
Get off.
ترجل.
Bai Ze.
باي زي.
Open the door, Bai Ze.
افتح الباب يا باي زي.
Bai Ze. Open the door.
باي زي.  افتح الباب.
She's worried about you
إنها قلقة عليك
as if I'm going to eat you up alive.
كأنني سأكلك حيا.
She's right.
انها محقة.
Knock it off
اغلقه
or I will eat you up.
أو سوف أكلك.
Try me.
جربني.
Are you taking my joke seriously?
هل تأخذ مزاحتي على محمل الجد؟
I told you.
أخبرتك.
No matter what you said,
لا يهم ما قلته ،
I will take them seriously.
سوف آخذهم على محمل الجد.
Bai Ze.
باي زي.
I like you.
أنا معجب بك.
Very much.
كثيرا جدا.
- Bai Ze. - Let's leave, Martial Sister.
- باي زي.  - دعنا نرحل ، أخت عسكرية.
Bai Ze.
باي زي.
Sister-in-law.
أخت الزوج أو اخت الزوجة.
Hmph!
همف!
Martial Sister, mind your step.
الأخت العرفية ، اهتم بخطوتك.
Never let me see her again.
لا تدعني أراها مرة أخرى.
Otherwise...
خلاف ذلك...
Sister-in-law.
أخت الزوج أو اخت الزوجة.
Shut it.
أغلقه.
Eldest Martial Brother said
قال الأخ الأكبر
I should call her sister-in-law.
يجب أن أتصل بأخت زوجها.
You!
أنت!
Miss Linyue.
ملكة جمال لينيو.
Bai Ze is kind of outspoken and direct.
باي زي هو نوع من الصراحة والمباشرة.
Please don't take it personally.
من فضلك لا تأخذ الأمر على محمل شخصي.
If you don't want to deliver the food,
إذا كنت لا تريد توصيل الطعام ،
I will do it for you.
وسوف نفعل ذلك لك.
That's our duty.
هذا هو واجبنا.
Don't you outsider meddle.
لا تتدخل من الخارج.
Hey.
يا.
You said you could deliver the food for me?
قلت أنه يمكنك توصيل الطعام لي؟
Go ahead.
تفضل.
What are you doing, Martial Sister?
ماذا تفعلين أيتها الأخت العسكرية؟
Be quiet.
كن هادئاً.
Give it to her.
أعطها لها.
Why dawdle? Go now.
لماذا تباطأ؟  اذهب الآن.
- Now? - Cut your crap and move.
- الآن؟  - قطع حماقة الخاص بك والتحرك.
Yes.
نعم.
This.
هذا.
Master! Bad news!
يتقن!  اخبار سيئة!
Miss Qinghuan triggered the Qingyun Mist in the Heavenly Dungeon.
تسببت ملكة جمال تشينغوان في إطلاق ضباب تشينغيون في الزنزانة السماوية.
The Heavenly Dungeon is a forbidden place.
الزنزانة السماوية مكان ممنوع.
How did she get in there?
كيف دخلت هناك؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
(Heavenly Dungeon)
(الزنزانة السماوية)
Father, Qinghuan stole my jade pendant
الأب ، تشينغوان سرق قلادة اليشم الخاصة بي
and trespassed in the forbidden area.
وتجاوزوا المنطقة المحرمة.
Master, it was...
سيدي ، كان ...
Bai Ze.
باي زي.
What are you doing, Bai Ze?
ماذا تفعل يا باي زي؟
I want to save her.
اريد انقاذها.
This is the forbidden area.
هذه هي المنطقة المحرمة.
You can't just break into it.
لا يمكنك اقتحامها فقط.
Are you insane? Qinghuan trespassed in the area
هل أنت مجنون؟  تجاوزت Qinghuan المنطقة
out of evil intentions. She must be...
من النوايا الشريرة.  يجب عليها ان تكون...
No, she won't.
لا ، لن تفعل ذلك.
Bai Ze.
باي زي.
Think carefully.
فكر جيدًا.
The forbidden area is set up with dangerous machinations.
المنطقة المحرمة معدة بمكائد خطيرة.
You will get hurt severely.
سوف تتأذى بشدة.
I won't regret this.
لن أندم على هذا.
(Heavenly Dungeon)
(الزنزانة السماوية)
Qinghuan.
تشينغوان.
Qinghuan, wake up?
Qinghuan ، استيقظ؟
Qinghuan. Wake up. Don't scare me.
تشينغوان.  استيقظ.  لا تخيفني.
♪Wandered off from the crowd♪
تجول بعيدًا عن الحشد ♪
♪As more wonderful things await♪
♪ كما تنتظر المزيد من الأشياء الرائعة
♪A sunset from the past resurfaced♪
انعكاس غروب الشمس من الماضي
♪Thousands of sailboats drifted in the sea of clouds♪
جرفت آلاف المراكب الشراعية في بحر السحب
♪And docked at different piers♪
♪ ورست على أرصفة مختلفة ♪
♪Only the catkin willow and my graying hair remained♪
فقط صفصاف القطة وشعري الشيب بقي
♪Let's take on♪
♪ لنأخذ
♪Another year♪
♪ سنة أخرى ♪
♪I traveled alone toward daytime as I waved aside the night♪
سافرت لوحدي في النهار بينما كنت ألوح جانباً في الليل
♪The tapping rain♪
مطر التنصت ♪
♪Awakened the sorrow♪
أيقظ الحزن
♪I'm crying out in loneliness amid pandemonium♪
♪ أنا أبكي في عزلة وسط الهرج والمرج
♪I endured countless ordeals from worldly entanglement♪
لقد تحملت محن لا حصر لها من التشابك الدنيوي ♪
♪Knowing how difficult things are for the first time♪
معرفة مدى صعوبة الأمور لأول مرة ♪
♪After you overcome the vicissitudes of life♪
بعد أن تتغلب على تقلبات الحياة
♪Only then do you understand the fickleness of the world♪
"عندها فقط تفهم تقلب العالم"
♪I wanted to enjoy the years but it turned into a disaster overnight♪
♪ أردت الاستمتاع بالسنوات لكنها تحولت إلى كارثة بين عشية وضحاها
♪Knowing that I can't turn back time♪
♪ مع العلم أنني لا أستطيع العودة بالزمن ♪
♪You would not be intoxicated by sorrow♪
لن تسكر بالحزن
♪Until you were embroiled in love♪
حتى تتورط في الحب ♪
♪I wanted to enjoy the years but it turned into a disaster overnight♪
♪ أردت الاستمتاع بالسنوات لكنها تحولت إلى كارثة بين عشية وضحاها
♪Knowing that I can't turn back time♪
♪ مع العلم أنني لا أستطيع العودة بالزمن ♪
♪You would not be intoxicated by sorrow♪
لن تسكر بالحزن
♪Until you were embroiled in love♪
حتى تتورط في الحب ♪